bloom.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy and Security

Bloom.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We take the following steps to ensure that you can use our site with confidence. If you have any additional questions about protecting your information and privacy please contact us so we can help you.

Bloom.com is a general audience web site, intended for users over 18 years of age. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Bloom.com and its operational service partners collects and use your personal information to provide Bloom.com services, verify your identity upon sign in, customize your experience, identify your Content, communicate marketing and promotional announcements to our members, process orders and deliver products requested, conduct customer service, and enforce our policies. It is possible that Bloom may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from Bloom.com and its affiliates. Bloom.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Bloom.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Bloom.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Bloom.com does not disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

We may collect passive information on products browsed and we analyze this information in aggregate to ensure the Site is merchandised in a manner that adds the most convenience and value to our customers. When an order is placed, we collect basic information including your name, home address, phone, email address and credit card information. We use this information to confirm your order and to respond to any questions you may have. Where required, we also share this information with certain intermediaries (freight carriers, shipping companies and product manufacturers) strictly to process and ship your order.

Bloom.com may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Bloom.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Bloom.com, including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Bloom.com or the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Bloom.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Bloom.com abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Bloom.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through 128 bit encryption.

**Secure Sockets Layering (SSL)**

Our website uses Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. Because we use SSL, placing an order online at our website is just as safe as giving your credit card number over the phone.

**Changes to this Statement**

Bloom.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Bloom.com will use your personal information, Bloom.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Bloom.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Bloom.com is protecting your information.

**Cookies**

Acceptance of cookies is not a requirement to browse the Site; however, our shopping cart does require the acceptance of cookies to work properly. Cookies are never used to store sensitive customer information such as names, addresses, passwords or credit card numbers.

**Friend's Email addresses**

There are "e-mail to a friend" and "invite a friend" features on the Site that allow you to easily share product or other valuable information with your friends. We may retain these e-mail addresses and use them to process BloomDollar credits that you may earn on the Site. We may also use these e-mail addresses to facilitate current and future social networking features on the Site. Your friend may be notified when you open your account and when you make purchases.

**Control your Personal Information**

Bloom.com offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may notify us of your preferences by emailing [beautyadvice@bloom.com](mailto:beautyadvice@bloom.com). Please be sure to provide complete account information and the same email address that you use to access Bloom.com so we can identify you in our records.

You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Bloom.com by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.

In return for making a purchase, registering or telling us more about yourself at the Site, we offer to keep you informed of new and ongoing benefits, exclusive sales and promotions and other customer-only benefits. We appreciate any additional, optional information you are willing to share with us. This optional information helps us tailor your experience at the Site, showing you content that we think might be interesting to you. Depending on the information you give us, we will also provide you with relevant information to enhance your experience on the site.

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information in the manner we describe. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on the Site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice and will apply to all users of the Site.

This Statement of Privacy applies to Bloom.com and Bloom Web sites and governs data collection and usage at these sites and services on these sites; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. We encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Bloom.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Bloom.com Web site.

**Additional Links**

Please contact us at [beautyadvice@bloom.com](mailto:beautyadvice@bloom.com) if you have further questions about our Privacy Policy or you have any suggestions on how we can improve your shopping experience with us. We always enjoy hearing from you! Thank you for shopping at Bloom.com

**Sincerely,    
The Bloom.com Team**

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is December 1, 2010.

Copyright © Xuba LLC. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
